<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Drunk Fist</title>
    <description>The drunk fist is my progress from a drunken developer into a full time carer who has stopped smoking, stopped drinking and started to take up boxing, muay thai, bjj, mma and generally just trying to be better.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:51:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>new year - old me and thedrunkfist podcast coming soon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;New Year - Old Me and Podcast coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, as January is in full swing I have decided to try and blog a bit more to go with my Instagram, Facebook and Twitter social media activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first post of the year is a good place to look back at 2016 and reflect and plan for 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created a video slideshow of &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/p/BO35Pcdg91P/&quot; title=&quot;2016 in review&quot;&gt;2016 in review&lt;/a&gt; that shows me how well I did last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weight was lost to a personal best level and I took up Muay Thai, BJJ and Yoga and things were positive despite it being a tricky year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just before Christmas I tailed off in terms of training and this year has started with a car accident among other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, New Year - Old Me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I intend to carry on with my martial arts and plan to only improve gradually this year just as I did last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No dad diets or plans that I will fail at as so many New Years have started off like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.thedrunkfist.com/blog/podcast/2017-01-12-thedrunkfist-podcast-0001_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;A thedrunkfist podcast &quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a huge fan of podcasts and as an ex developer and devops nerd I have decided to try out creating my own podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as this website I am going to record, host and deliver podcasts to document my journey and chat all things health and fitness, diet and nutrition, MMA, Muay Thai, BJJ, Kettlebells and anything else that comes up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I may even try and get some guests on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exciting stuff!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy new year!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/12/new-year-old-me-podcast-coming/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/12/new-year-old-me-podcast-coming/</guid>
        
        <category>#podcast</category>
        
        <category>#audio</category>
        
        <category>#video</category>
        
        <category>#muaythai</category>
        
        <category>#bjj</category>
        
        <category>#mma</category>
        
        <category>#nutrition</category>
        
        <category>#interviews</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New personal best!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So, I am very happy !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One year ago today, I weighed approximately 80 kg and I managed to deadlifts 80 kg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, yesterday I managed to dead lift 100 kg while weighing in at a much lighter 70kg!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://takeactionpt.net/&quot; title=&quot;take action personal training&quot;&gt;take action personal training&lt;/a&gt; for the photograph and the help in reaching this personal best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have not had much sleep this evening because in a few hours I have to visit the hospital with my mother for a very important scan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However I am staying very positive about this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have even submitted a form to Twitter to verify my account to attain the blue badge status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.thedrunkfist.com/blog/training/new-deadlift-pb_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;A dead lift personal-best&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still not finished, I intend to lift heavier and I aim to continue my training in Muay Thai and Brazilian jujitsu as well as my kettle bell training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank all the guys who are on the same mission as me and are helping me in terms of training and support at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onwards!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/08/30/new-deadlift-pb/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/08/30/new-deadlift-pb/</guid>
        
        <category>#pb</category>
        
        <category>#training</category>
        
        <category>#deadlift</category>
        
        <category>#muaythai</category>
        
        <category>#bjj</category>
        
        <category>#mma</category>
        
        <category>#nutrition</category>
        
        <category>#happy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>hit fit video</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As well as having an hours Muay Thai training I am also doing a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.takeactionpt.net/hitfit.html&quot;&gt;HIT FIT cardio class&lt;/a&gt; to boost my workouts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are run by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.takeactionpt.net&quot;&gt;Take Action Personal Training&lt;/a&gt; and are really good fun and an excellent workout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.thedrunkfist.com/blog/training/hit_fit_3_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;kicking pads&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not that impressed with my technique in this session/video as such but its more about fun and cardio after already doing special training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a video from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/U0kB35TlczI&quot;&gt;You Tube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe id=&quot;ytplayer&quot; type=&quot;text/html&quot; width=&quot;320&quot; height=&quot;320&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/O9D17pezWzo?autoplay=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/08/02/hit-fit/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/08/02/hit-fit/</guid>
        
        <category>#sleep</category>
        
        <category>#training</category>
        
        <category>#diet</category>
        
        <category>#muaythai</category>
        
        <category>#bjj</category>
        
        <category>#mma</category>
        
        <category>#nutrition</category>
        
        <category>#happy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New personal best!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So, I am very happy !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One year ago today, I weighed approximately 80 kg and I managed to deadlifts 80 kg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, yesterday I managed to dead lift 100 kg while weighing in at a much lighter 70kg!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://takeactionpt.net/&quot; title=&quot;take action personal training&quot;&gt;take action personal training&lt;/a&gt; for the photograph and the help in reaching this personal best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have not had much sleep this evening because in a few hours I have to visit the hospital with my mother for a very important scan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However I am staying very positive about this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have even submitted a form to Twitter to verify my account to attain the blue badge status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.thedrunkfist.com/blog/training/new-deadlift-pb_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;A dead lift personal-best&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still not finished, I intend to lift heavier and I aim to continue my training in Muay Thai and Brazilian jujitsu as well as my kettle bell training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank all the guys who are on the same mission as me and are helping me in terms of training and support at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onwards!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/07/30/new-deadlift-pb/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/07/30/new-deadlift-pb/</guid>
        
        <category>#pb</category>
        
        <category>#training</category>
        
        <category>#deadlift</category>
        
        <category>#muaythai</category>
        
        <category>#bjj</category>
        
        <category>#mma</category>
        
        <category>#nutrition</category>
        
        <category>#happy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Before and after</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to post a before and after photograph of myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The horrible picture on the left is me approximately five or six years ago and I guess I am weighing around 120 KG.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a full-time software engineer that let’s say I liked a drink and smoked cigarettes and a good time and used to play as hard as I worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I lived a very sedentary lifestyle, and as you can see I was not in the best physical shape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.thedrunkfist.com/blog/training/fatlad-to-now_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;before and after&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast forward a few years I gave up smoking first of all then started training with kettle bells and then took up boxing and that  progressed to training Muay Thai mostly now, I hit pads, I spar and I work on techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only that I have also taken up BJJ and MMA and I really look after my nutrition now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I now weigh 69 kg however, my new target is 65 kg and my journey as a martial artist has only just started at 41 years of age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onwards!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/07/27/before-and-after/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/07/27/before-and-after/</guid>
        
        <category>#sleep</category>
        
        <category>#training</category>
        
        <category>#diet</category>
        
        <category>#muaythai</category>
        
        <category>#bjj</category>
        
        <category>#mma</category>
        
        <category>#nutrition</category>
        
        <category>#happy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sleep,training and diet makes me happy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It would be fair to say that I am in the best shape physically and mentally for as long as I can remember.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has not been anti depressants, juice plus shakes or anything else that has helped. I have not won the lottery and life still throws all sorts at me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, it has been improved sleep, a clean diet and lots of fun exercises that have worked magic for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.thedrunkfist.com/blog/sleep/sleep_training_diet_happy_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;sleep,training and diet make me happy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Career wise being a software developer has had its benefits and I love building and learning new technical skills, but it took its toll with the sedentary lifestyle, the insomnia and the booze to knock you out and get you to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days I am a full time carer, which is not easy, but very rewarding, I am still writing code, but for the past few years I have taken up Kettlebell training which led to Boxing which led to Muay Thai which led to BJJ and MMA training and I love my new hobbies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This training has also led to an improved diet and the physical exertion has also improved my sleep no end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now combine all these things and you could say I have never been happier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep going old man! Keep going.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/07/17/sleep-training-diet-happy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/07/17/sleep-training-diet-happy/</guid>
        
        <category>#sleep</category>
        
        <category>#training</category>
        
        <category>#diet</category>
        
        <category>muaythai</category>
        
        <category>bjj</category>
        
        <category>mma</category>
        
        <category>nutrition</category>
        
        <category>happy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sleep on a Thursday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sleep matters. No, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Effects_of_sleep_deprivation_on_cognitive_performance&quot;&gt;really it does&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have had issues with sleep for years now but my recent training in &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muay_Thai&quot;&gt;Muay Thai&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brazilian_jiu-jitsu&quot;&gt;BJJ&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boxing&quot;&gt;Boxing&lt;/a&gt; added to my &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kettlebell&quot;&gt;Kettlebell&lt;/a&gt; workouts have really helped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a two-way thing too. A &lt;a href=&quot;http://us13.campaign-archive1.com/?u=f7fe20d352e4ace31643e717b&amp;amp;id=d0aa68ffe0&amp;amp;e=2180035b6b&quot;&gt;recent newsletter&lt;/a&gt; I received from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.takeactionpt.net&quot;&gt;Take Action Personal Training&lt;/a&gt; pointed this out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I feel rested and ready to start the day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/07/07/sleep-on-thursday/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/07/07/sleep-on-thursday/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The drunk fist website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So, The name drunk fist comes from the name of a test account I setup to test the Facebook Developer API toolkit. In layman’s terms, it was an account I setup for a work project years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The name ‘Drunk fist’ came from an old Kung Fu movie I saw and I liked the name and I decided to re-use it to start to blog about all things diet, nutrition, health and fitness. Basically anything interesting I find that’s not code related and too long to just share on social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am at the time of writing this blog post a 41-year-old man from Oxfordshire in the UK and have transitioned from being a full-time sedentary Software Developer and DevOps guy into being a full-time carer for my elderly mother and my brother who had a stroke a while back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of this progress has included my new diet, weight loss and interest in Boxing, Muay Thai, Brazillian Jui Jitsu, MMA and Kettlebells and generally just trying to navigate my middle years while being as fit and healthy in mind and body as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I have a couple of websites and blogs and the main one is hosted on blogger and has years of content and lives at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.solrevdev.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.solrevdev.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is very technical in nature and has been live for quite a long time and eventually I will migrate that away from the ageing blogger eco-system to a Github-hosted blog run from Jekyll as is this one is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, the boilerplate site is ready for the content to be imported to this location &lt;a href=&quot;http://solrevdev.github.io/&quot;&gt;http://solrevdev.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, as well as programming, system administration, DevOps and all things technical my relatively new pursuits are health and fitness and I have various social media accounts that are plotting my progress in Boxing, Muay Thai, Brazillian Jui Jitsu, MMA (mixed martial arts) and Kettlebell training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While social media such as Facebook, Twitter and Instagram are great for short form content I wanted a website and blog where  longer form posts about my interests and progress could live and well, this is it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/06/10/the-drunk-fist-website/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/06/10/the-drunk-fist-website/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
